The Amanda Steele Show.
Things I learned this week.
Yeah.
If you have a spider in your house,
did you know that apparently when you put it outside,
it dies because it's not meant to live outside.
It lived in the house.
And I am somebody who really be saving spiders
and I'd be thinking I'm saving spiders
and I didn't know that I was really sentencing them to death.
So spiders are our friends unless they can bite you.
And then that's a whole other conversation.
If you're in Australia, just ignore this message.
Um, did you know that the five heartbeats
was originally set up as a development deal
at Warner Brothers in 1988 with Keen and Ivory Wayans,
his brother Damon and others tapped to star.
But Warner passed on the project
and the Wayans moved on to then develop
and star in In Living Color instead.
So Eddie Kane could have been Keen and Ivory Wayans,
which I just, it would have been a completely different movie.
Things end up sometimes working out the way
that they are supposed to.
Now I thought this was a really great story.
Y'all know I am obsessed with the movie Coming to America.
It is my favorite movie of all time.
And I just didn't know that there was something
that could make me love the movie even more.
But I found out that Niall Rogers
was the songwriter, composer, and producer
of the Coming to America soundtrack.
He produced, he produced the whole thing.
I didn't know there was anything
that could make me love Coming to America more.
But boy, oh boy, that was it right there.
I never get tired of.
She's your...
you're...